{
    "subject": "resource/Maradona_by_Kusturica",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Maradona by Kusturica",
    "human_readable": "The label of Maradona by Kusturica is Maradona by Kusturica.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9067574143409729,
            "question": "Who is the subject of the film 'Maradona by Kusturica'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8539320826530457,
            "question": "What genre is 'Maradona by Kusturica' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.76506108045578,
            "question": "What kind of audience might be interested in watching 'Maradona by Kusturica'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7581647634506226,
            "question": "What can we infer about the relationship between Kusturica and Maradona based on the title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5276074409484863,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Kusturica?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4694008529186249,
            "question": "Are there any other films by Kusturica that you know of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33047088980674744,
            "question": "How might a film like this contribute to our understanding of Maradona's legacy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31474533677101135,
            "question": "Why might a filmmaker choose to make a film about a specific person like Maradona?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2791222333908081,
            "question": "What elements of filmmaking might be used to tell Maradona's story effectively?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.024877216666936874,
            "question": "Can you think of any other films that have focused on the lives of famous athletes?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Maradona by Kusturica is Maradona by Kusturica.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2728_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What elements of filmmaking might be used to tell Maradona's story effectively?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2728_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why might a filmmaker choose to make a film about a specific person like Maradona?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2728_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might a film like this contribute to our understanding of Maradona's legacy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2728_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2728_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2728_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2728_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2728_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2728_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2728_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2728_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2728_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2728_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2728_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in the requested format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as it mentions \"Maradona by Kusturica\" multiple times and describes it as a portrait of Diego Maradona."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe query asks to confirm if the label of \"Maradona by Kusturica\" in the context refers correctly to a film or documentary about Diego Maradona. The documents describe various aspects and details related to this work, confirming it as a portrait of Diego Maradona created by director Emir Kusturica, thus supporting the triple statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}